Elisabeth Semel Papers
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Issues and Topics, 1977-2009; nam_apap332-2; 3 cubic ft.
  - Costs (2 of 2), 1991-1995; 1998-2006; 2009; Undated; nam_apap332-2_5 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Counsel - Pre 2000, 1990; 1993; 1996-2000; Undated; nam_apap332-2_6 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Counsel - 1990s-2000s, 1993; 1997-1998; 2002-2004; Undated; nam_apap332-2_7 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Counsel (1 of 2), 2000; nam_apap332-2_8 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Counsel (2 of 2), 2000; nam_apap332-2_9 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Counsel - January-June (1 of 2), 2001; nam_apap332-2_10 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Counsel - January-June (2 of 2), 2001; nam_apap332-2_11 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Counsel - July-December, 2001; Undated; nam_apap332-2_12 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Counsel, 2002; nam_apap332-2_13 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Counsel - 2003, 2002-2004; nam_apap332-2_14 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Counsel - 2004, 2004-2005; nam_apap332-2_15 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Counsel - 2005-2007, 2006-2007; Undated; nam_apap332-2_16 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Crime - Prevention, 1990-1998; 2000; 2002; Undated; nam_apap332-2_17 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Crime - Public Perception, 1992-1998; 2000; nam_apap332-2_18 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Crime - Statistics, 1992-2000; 2002-2003; 2008; nam_apap332-2_19 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Habeas - Loss of, 1991-1992; 1995-1997; 1999-2001; 2007; Undated; nam_apap332-2_20 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Innocence - Exoneration After Execution, 1999-2001; 2004-2005; nam_apap332-2_21 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Innocence - Life After Death Row, 1998-2004; nam_apap332-2_22 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Innocence - Non-DNA, 1998-2004; nam_apap332-2_23 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Innocence - Overviews, 1993-1994; 1997-2001; 2005-2007; nam_apap332-2_24 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Innocence - Protection Act, 1999-2002; 2004-2005; nam_apap332-2_25 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Juveniles - Pre 2000 (1 of 2), 1994-1996; 1998; 2007; Undated; nam_apap332-2_26 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Juveniles - Pre 2000 (2 of 2), 1992; 1995-1999; Undated; nam_apap332-2_27 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Juveniles, 2000; nam_apap332-2_28 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Juveniles, 2001; nam_apap332-2_29 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Juveniles, 2002; nam_apap332-2_30 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Juveniles - 2002-2003, 2002-2004; nam_apap332-2_31 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Juveniles - 2004, Simmons, nam_apap332-2_32 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Juveniles, 2004-2005; nam_apap332-2_33 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Kendall, George Speeches, 1996-1998; nam_apap332-2_34 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Mentally Ill, 1998-2007; nam_apap332-2_35 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Mentally Retarded - Pre 2000, 1991; 1993; 1997-1999; nam_apap332-2_36 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Mentally Retarded - 2000, 2000-2001; nam_apap332-2_37 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Mentally Retarded - 2001, Undated; nam_apap332-2_38 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Mental Retardation - 2000, 2002, 2002-2003; Undated; nam_apap332-2_39 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Mental Retardation - 2004, 2004-2005; 2007; nam_apap332-2_40 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Mental Retardation - Atkins Response, 2002-2003; nam_apap332-2_41 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Mental Retardation - HRW Report 2001 (1 of 2), 2000-2001; nam_apap332-2_42 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Mental Retardation - HRW Report 2001 (2 of 2), 2000-2001; nam_apap332-2_43 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Mental Retardation - Legislation, 2001; nam_apap332-2_44 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Non-Death, Chicago Tribune, October, 2004; nam_apap332-2_45 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Opinion - Anti-Death Penalty: Growing Public Opinion, 2002-2006; nam_apap332-2_46 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Opinion - Anti-Death Penalty, 2008; nam_apap332-2_47 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Opinion - Conservative Opposition, 2000-2001; 2003-2005; Undated; nam_apap332-2_48 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Opinion - Editorials, Anti-Pre 2000, 1977; 1982; 1990-2000; Undated; nam_apap332-2_49 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Opinion - Editorials, Anti-Pre 2001, 1999-2000; Undated; nam_apap332-2_50 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Opinion - Editorials, Anti-2000-2001 (1 of 2), Undated; nam_apap332-2_51 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Opinion - Editorials, Anti-2000-2001 (2 of 2), nam_apap332-2_52 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Opinion - Editorials, Anti-2004-2005, 2002-2005; 2007; Undated; nam_apap332-2_53 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Opinion - Editorials, Anti-2005-2007, nam_apap332-2_54 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Opinion - International, 1999-2000, 1996-2000; Undated; nam_apap332-2_55 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Opinion - International, 2001, 2000-2001; nam_apap332-2_56 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Opinion - International, 2002-2003, nam_apap332-2_57 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Opinion - International, 2004, 2001-2004; nam_apap332-2_58 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Opinion - Pro, 1977; 1999-2002; 2004; 2006; Undated; nam_apap332-2_59 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Opinion - Public, Through 2000, 1992; 1995; 1997-2000; 2004; Undated; nam_apap332-2_60 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Opinion - Public, 2001-2002, Undated; nam_apap332-2_61 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Opinion - Public, 2003-2004, Undated; nam_apap332-2_62 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Opinion - Public, 2005-2006, 2001; 2005-2007; nam_apap332-2_63 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Politicians, 1993; 1995; 1999-2005; Undated; nam_apap332-2_64 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Prison Conditions California (1 of 2), 1991; 1994-2001; 2004-2006; Undated; nam_apap332-2_65 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Prison Conditions California (2 of 2), 1985; 1987; 1991-1995; 1997-1999; Undated; nam_apap332-2_66 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Profiles, 1995; 1998-200; Undated; nam_apap332-2_67 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Prosecution Misconduct, 1992-1994; 1997-2005; 2007; Undated; nam_apap332-2_68 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Prosecution Misconduct - Chicago Tribune, Pre 2000, 1999; nam_apap332-2_69 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Prosecution Misconduct - Chicago Tribune, 2000-2001; 2003; 2005; Undated; nam_apap332-2_70 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Prosecution Misconduct - Pittsburgh Post Gazette, 1999; nam_apap332-2_71 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Prosecution Politics, 1999-2003; nam_apap332-2_72 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Race - Death Penalty Articles (1 of 2), 1991; 1994-2004; Undated; nam_apap332-2_73 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Race - Death Penalty Articles (2 of 2), 1992-1994; 1996-1997; 1999-2001; 2003; Undated; nam_apap332-2_74 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Race - General, 1997-2004; 2007; Undated; nam_apap332-2_75 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Race - Official Studies and Law Reviews, 1986-1987; 1991; 1995-1998; nam_apap332-2_76 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Race - Prisons, 1991-1994; 1997-1998; 2000; 2005; Undated; nam_apap332-2_77 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Religion - Catholics, 1992; 1996-2000; 2004; nam_apap332-2_78 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Religion - Catholics, 2000-2007; Undated; nam_apap332-2_79 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Religious Views - General, 2000-2004; 2007; Undated; nam_apap332-2_80 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Religion - Jews, 1996-1997; 1999-2002; 2007-2009; Undated; nam_apap332-2_81 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Resource Centers, 1996; nam_apap332-2_82 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Statistics Through 2001, 1990-2001; Undated; nam_apap332-2_83 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Statistics Through 2007, 2002-2007; nam_apap332-2_84 (Box 5, Folder 8)